If I need to, yeah, I'll figure that out.
I will call it the order of the mind, especially until the authority board meeting for Monday, March 7, 2022.
We'll have invocation by Chaplain of the Mind and Fire Department.
Mr. Brandon Fletcher, he will be introduced by Chief Robert Wright.
Good evening. This is Brandon Fletcher. He's with her place here at Jawsville.
And who is a moved off the home city area.
He's a 2008 graduate of Iowa High School. He's graduate of OSU.
That would be a chance.
And his graduate of OSU are a Christian college.
Him and his wife, Katie, have two boys, Bronson and Brachston.
And we're proud of the head of him as our new chaplain for the party.
Thank you all.
It's definitely an honor to be able to serve in any capacity.
We'll go further.
Father, we are so thankful for a group of men and women who are passionate about local community.
And God, we are honored that you and trust leadership to us.
And Father, we know that our goal, our initiative in life, is to love others and to love you.
And so we pray that tonight you will give wisdom.
That you'll give courageous leadership insights.
Whatever needs to happen.
And you will put that forth here.
And let us follow through to make this community great.
So make this community what it should be.
Father, we love you.
Our prayers that will be more like Jesus.
And says name and prayer.
Amen.
Father, I believe you should apply the United States as a mayor.
And two, three of the brothers, for which it stands.
One nation under God and a missile with a liberty and justice for all.
Thanks, Brayton.
Welcome, Board.
For both of you.
But I'm scheduled personal appearances.
We have two Tim Morris and Brett Kevin.
I think Tyler talked to them.
We talked to them again.
We'll take care of them.
We'll move on to five.
The agenda of staff recommends we approve of six and seven.
Motion.
Second.
Okay.
Double.
Hi.
Davis.
Murder.
Yes.
Sunder.
And he's dead.
Hi.
We thought this means a little quick.
I think maybe he's slow.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm just saying eight, budget, number 22, that's 19, MSUA,
Meadering. That's for my get. All right. Meadering has a 2008 up 150 that has a
blown radiator and transmission. So, it's ground all that money for them. We received $13,000
from scrap metal in 19,000. The insurance recovery money will not mend that. It's
new revenue and then take 1632 from the supplies account to allow them to buy a new 22,
that won't get you for the lead in truck. So, does that go to beds or does that something
mean by local or... You'll go to state beds. So, on some state beds, you don't have to get
multiple beds. Is there any of our local dealers on that?
There's a lot of finance for you, man. You can just improve that. I'll make motion.
Second. Pardon? Hi. Nice to meet you. Hi. Davis. Hi. Thanks, my mind. You're nail-stratting
claim and the Davis right for my claim for GRD or your licensing. So, what we have before you
was a claim from Larry Bort with good else trying for $1,329.30 in another invoice from DWT for $61,411.
These folks have been working extensively of the last months. Specifically, they analyzed the
GRDA's response to our initial study report comments. They prepared for the intended the GRDA's
January 14th sedimentation study technical conference. They filed our extensive January 14th
comments and concerns related to the proposed sediment study and analyzed the positive January 18th
decision by the DC circuit. So, we're asking for the Council's approval for these claims tonight.
And we are contractual contractual, contractual, I'll get a pay to you. We are contractual, I'll
get it to pay. I'll make a motion. Second. Hi. Hi. All right. All right. 10 Resolution CC-2022-04
and MSU-8022-01, the joint resolution, delegating settlement claims payment authority to the city manager
and trust manager. So, this is an item that's going to be on both the changes because both
entities are improving or going to address their decision. This is a result of our last executive
segment and we're going to discuss the claim that it's over $500 in the council.
At that time, it's suggested that we review our resolution and raise the amount that the city manager has set them out of $4 to afford up to $2,500, so this resolution does that.
It's essentially a original resolution just changing the amount that he's authorized to sell.
I'll make a motion.
All second.
Hi.
Eight.
All right.
11.
One utility easement from Pitt Abysian Property LLC, as presented.
Approved claim of $20 for record the easement at the Auto County Clerk Office.
Tyler.
We're Ben.
So Tyler and I talked about this today, and this is quite simply the property owner.
The owner had requested that we set the transformer closer to the actual unit, which would be using the power.
It's not a house.
I can't say the house.
Tyler.
And therefore, the city had to modify the easement to include this extended range.
So that's all we're doing is recording this easement.
This is the ADD there.
It is.
They are granting the easement to the city.
But we're required to approve saying that we're willing to.
We're willing to take that.
Motion to approve the adjusted easement.
Second.
All right.
On the second.
Yes.
Thank you.
This is harder than it looks.
Hi.
Harder.
Every day.
You stay.
12.
The new business of any of those reasons since the posting of this agenda.
13.
Staff reports.
14.
Trust the community announcements.
15.
Germany.
Some of.
Second.
David.
He's there.
All right.